{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M2L6a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the adjectives that describe the feelings. ",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "yagnr",
                    "answer": "angry"
                },
                {
                    "question": "guyhrn",
                    "answer": "hungry"
                },
                {
                    "question": "payhp",
                    "answer": "happy"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ithtsyr",
                    "answer": "thirsty"
                },
                {
                    "question": "etdri",
                    "answer": "tired"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ads",
                    "answer": "sad"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP5M3L13a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the words",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "terawllaf",
                    "answer": "waterfall"
                },
                {
                    "question": "noumatin",
                    "answer": "mountain"
                },
                {
                    "question": "lhil",
                    "answer": "hill"
                },
                {
                    "question": "baceh",
                    "answer": "beach"
                },
                {
                    "question": "evac",
                    "answer": "cave"
                },
                {
                    "question": "oertfs",
                    "answer": "forest"
                },
                {
                    "question": "danils",
                    "answer": "island"
                },
                {
                    "question": "eakl",
                    "answer": "lake"
                },
                {
                    "question": "erriv",
                    "answer": "river"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}